Guide to the Vassar College Class Records, 1865-2021
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1949, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - "1948 and 1949 40th! A Compendium of Songs,", 1989 (Box 1)
  - "50th reunion schedule 1948 and 1949,", 1999 (Box 1)
  - Badges collected by Ann Hutchinson (VC 1949), undated (Box 1)
  - Brochure for Vassar Reunion, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Class notice from class secretary Gertrude Garnsey, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1949 honor roll, undated (Box 1)
  - Class photo album, undated (Box 1)
  - Class photo album, undated (Box 2)
  - Comic/letter from Nancy Reed Schafer (VC 1949), 1999 Jun 24 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence from F. Fergusson to Ann Hutchinson (VC 1949), undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence from F. Fergusson to Jane Howard Guernsey (VC 1949), undated (Box 1)
  - "Directions for Commencement,", 1948 Jun 26 (Box 1)
  - Invitation from F. Fergusson to "Vassar College Society Luncheon,", undated (Box 1)
  - List of 1949 slate of officers 1994-1999 / 45th reunion chairpersons (Box 1)
  - "Memory Lane - 60th Vassar Reunion,", 2009 Jun 5 (Box 1)
  - Menu for 1948/1949 reunion at the Culinary Inst. of America, 1999 Jun 3 (Box 1)
  - Photographs of alumnae, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Reader's Diatribe,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Ahoy and a Girl,", 1946 Oct 4 (Box 1)
  - Program for "Beggar on Horseback,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "De Profundis,", 1948 May 1 (Box 1)
  - Program for "Fedora Day,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Memorial Service for deceased members of Classes of 1948/1949,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Overture,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Six Shakes of a Lamb's Tale,", 1948 Feb 20 (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Creative Arts in Contemporary Society, 1948 Feb 27 (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Hallelujah Chorus Line - a 50th Reunion Production,", 1999 Jun 4 (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Merchant of Yonkers,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Sad Shepherd,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Skin of Our Teeth,", 1946 Mar 9 (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Spiral Weekend,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Volpone,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for the 123rd annual meeting of AAVC, 1994 Jun 11 (Box 1)
  - Program for the 128th annual meeting of AAVC, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Program for Vassar Reunion, 1999 (Box 1)
  - "Raymond Song Sheets 50th Reunion 1948-'49,", 1999 (Box 1)
  - Reunion chapel service and sheet music, 1999 (Box 1)
  - "Songs for the 1948-1949 Antiques Roadshow - 60th reunion,", 2010 Jun 6; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "Songs sung at Vassar 1945-1949,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1950, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1950 financial records, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1950 reunion updates, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1950 spring break photo, undated (Box 1)
  - Information on class of 1950 - marital status, address, children, etc., undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous photographs of 1950 at Vassar, undated; [2 envelopes] (Box 1)
  - Photographs of children of Edna (Geer) Illsley (VC 1950), undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "The Last Straw,", undated (Box 1)
  - Scholarship information + poster, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1951, [2.6 cubic feet (4 boxes)]
  - Binder - "The Shirley Oakes Butler Scholarship 1986-2009" Vol. 1 (Box 4)
  - Binder - "The Shirley Oakes Butler Scholarship 2009-2021" Vol. 2 (Box 4)
  - Scrapbook - "Class of 1951 Archives 1951-2001: 1951-1986" Vol. 1 (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook - "Class of 1951 Archives 1951-2001: 1986-1999" Vol. 2 (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook - "Class of 1951 Archives 1951-2001: 1996-2001" Vol. 3 (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook - "Class of 1951 Archives 2001-2006," (Box 2)
  - Scrapbook - "Class of 1951 Archives 2001-2006," (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook - "Class of 1951 Archives 2011-2016," (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook - "Class of 1951 Archives 2016-2021," (Box 4)
- Class of 1952, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1952 directory - 31st reunion, June 1983 (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Katherine (Malone) Harrington (VC 1952, undated (Box 1)
  - "Polly Parsons meets the 1948 Freshmen" newspaper article, undated (Box 1)
  - Sealed book - "1952" with umbrella on the cover, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar G-Stringer Reunion" book, 2004 Jun 4 (Box 1)
  - "Vassar Vista" Class of 1952, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1953, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - CD - "Songs from Soph Party and Junior Party,", undated; [2 CDs] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1953 financial records, undated (Box 1)
  - Green owl stationary (blank), undated (Box 1)
  - "Junior Party: Manhattan Cowers!,", 1951 Nov 9 (Box 1)
  - Notices to the class of 1953, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Playbill for Sophomore party: Mind Your Own Business!,", undated (Box 1)
  - Treasurer's ledger, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar 1953 35+1 Reunion 1989" booklet (Box 1)
- Class of 1954, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - No materials
- Class of 1955, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class book, undated (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - Class of 1955 Reunion Weekend, 1968 Jun (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "See Here '55", 1951 (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Cynthia P. Hayward (VC 1955), undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Joan Waffle (VC 1955), undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1956, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Article - "VC Student Attends N. Y. Times Forum,", undated (Box 1)
  - CD - "From Here to Eternithree, Hellbent for Heaven: Sophomore & Junior Party 1956,", undated (Box 1)
  - CD - "we remember...,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar 1956 Reunion 1987" alumnae list (Box 1)
- Class of 1957, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Article about alumna - "Precision Portraits,", undated (Box 1)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - VC 93rd Commencement program, 1957 Jun 10 (Box 1)
- Class of 1958, [1 cubic foot (3 boxes)]
  - 25th reunion booklet / class questionnaires, 1983 (Boxes 2-3)
  - Article - "Vassar, 1958, looks at the world of 1958,", undated (Box 1)
  - Clipping - "Anne Goes to Vassar," Seventeen, 1955 Mar (Oversize Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "From Vassar,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1959, [0.6 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - "1959 graduation photographs (baccalaureate too)," (Box 2)
  - Booklet - "See Here 1959 - A Vassar Connection,", undated (Box 1)
  - Audiocassette: Class of 1959 - 25th reunion, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Audiocassette: "1959's future: Where will our world be in 2009 - our 50th?,", undated; [2 copies] (Box 2)
  - "Extra slides used in slide show 25th reunion,", 1984 Jun 1 (Box 2)
  - Slides: beer-bike race, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Slides: Class of 1959 "people" shots used at 25th reunion, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Slides: Class of 1959 at 10th reunion, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Slides: dedication of Noyes, undated (Box 2)
  - Slides: Founder's Day, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Slides: Mr. Brooks' picnic for his senior English seminar, undated (Box 2)
  - Slides: shower for Elise Rosenberry, undated (Box 2)
  - Slides: ski trip in Bromley, VT, 1956 (Box 2)
  - Slides: some members of the class of 1959, undated (Box 2)
  - Slides: soph Fathers' weekend, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Slides: soph party 1959 "Zapathy,", 1957 (Box 2)
  - Slides: spring vacation - Darlene Spencer, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Tapes: "all scenery + buildings,", 1955-1959 (Box 2)
  - Videocassette: Class of 1959 25th reunion, 1984; [2 tapes] (Box 2)
- Class of 1960, [0.7 cubic feet (2 boxes)]
  - Article - "Elizabeth Bowen at Vassar - reprinted from Mademoiselle,", undated (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "Vassar 1960 reflects on 45 years of work/family experience - Reunion 2005,", [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Card from Terry O'Berry concerning daisy chain, undated (Box 1)
  - CD (unknown contents) and photo sheet from 1960 reunion, undated (Box 1)
  - CD: Interview with Ann Snyder Harrod (VC 1960) by Betty Daniels, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1960 obituaries of classmates and memorial service booklets, 1980-2010s (Box 1)
  - Class of 1960 photographs from 50th reunion, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1960 reunion memorabilia collected by Terry Cabot, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1960 reunion photographs - binder, undated (Box 2)
  - Daisy handkerchief, undated (Box 1)
  - "Invitation to join daisy chain" letter, 1960 (Box 1)
  - Negatives: 25th reunion, 1985 Jun 7 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper article on 1958 daisy chain (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clipping - "Vassar picks 21 sophomores for Daisy Chain on June 9,", undated (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Alumnae Names in the News,", undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Terry O'Berry in 1958 - publicity photo for daisy chain (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Vassar daisy chain, 1958 Jun 9 (Box 1)
  - Records/photographs from class of 1960 35th reunion, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Slides: Vassar 1960 brunch, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1961, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1961 address directory, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1961 reunion binder + photographs of campus + ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Drawings by Barbara Bellin for 50th reunion book, 2011 (Oversize Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Services for Seniors,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Offbeat,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Report of the anonymous questionnaire prepared for 35th reunion" class of 1961, 1996; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Vassar Centennial, undated (Box 1)
  - "The Vassar Centennial Class at Mid-life" 25th reunion questionnaire responses, 1986 (Box 1)
- Class of 1962, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Advertisement for book - "Good Abode,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1962 25th reunion report binder, 1987 Jun (Box 1)
  - Class of 1962 directory, 1970 (Box 1)
  - Drawing of the library, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Letter about library to class from Martha Nettleton Behr (class rep 1962), undated (Box 1)
  - "The Way We Were at Vassar College 1958-1962,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1963, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - 1963 baseball cap, undated (Box 1)
  - AAVC newsletter, fall council meeting, 1970 Oct 14 (Box 1)
  - Article - "Goheen Cites Value of Liberal Arts as VC awards 324 Diplomas,", undated (Box 1)
  - Article - "Men of Vassar,", undated (Box 1)
  - Article - "Stephen Dedalus at Vassar,", 1974 Dec 22 (Box 1)
  - Article - "the Making of a Vassar Man,", undated (Box 1)
  - CD - "Vassar 1963 in Wisconsin 2002,", 2002 Jul 18 (Box 1)
  - Class ephemera, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1963 30th reunion booklet, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 1)
  - Copy of no. 74 "Vassar Views,", undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence from President Blanding to Jill Spiller (VC 1963), undated (Box 1)
  - Development survey - "Attitudes and Opinions about Vassar,", undated (Box 1)
  - Drawings of campus, undated (Box 1)
  - Invitation to Junior Prom, 1962 Mar 10 (Box 1)
  - Jill Spiller 1963 basketball certification, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Jill Spiller 1963 report card, undated (Box 1)
  - Letter from Linda A. Fairstein to Jill Spiller (VC 1963), undated (Box 1)
  - List of Gifford Visiting Writers, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Misc illustrations/cartoons, undated (Box 1)
  - Notice - officers available to support freshmen, undated (Box 1)
  - Notice for "Rock and Roll party,", undated (Box 1)
  - Notice from American College Poetry Society to Jill Spiller (VC 1963), undated (Box 1)
  - Notice to alumnae/parents from A. Simpson about racial justice sit-in, 1969 Nov (Box 1)
  - Notice to the parents of VC freshmen, undated (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "The AAVC and You,", undated (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "Vassar for Men?,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "Command Performance,", undated (Box 1)
  - Program for "23761,", 1962 Feb 23 (Box 1)
  - Program for 1961 centennial convocation, 1961 Oct 12 (Box 1)
  - Program for 99th commencement - conferring of degrees, 1963 (Box 1)
  - Program for a Conference on Contemporary Arts, undated (Box 1)
  - Program for a vocal recital by Patricia Kennedy (VC 1963), undated (Box 1)
  - Program for Baccalaureate Vassar Service, 1963 Jun 1 (Box 1)
  - Report from Commission on Higher Ed. of Vassar, undated (Box 1)
  - "Salve song" lyrics, undated (Box 1)
  - Sheet music to "Vassar Alma Mater,", undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar - A Student's Perspective" admissions material, undated (Box 1)
  - "Vassar Alumnae Magazine - A Half Century of Vassar Opinion,", undated (Box 1)
  - Vassar patch, undated (Box 1)
  - VC Commencement program, 1963 (Box 1)
  - VC Presidential inauguration notice, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1964, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Commencement directions for academic procession, 1964 (Box 1)
  - "Vassar Questionnaire Results" (VC 1964), undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1965, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate service pamphlet, 1965 (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "See Here 1965" (photographs of class members), undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1965 class meeting transcript, undated; [4 packets] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1965 class meeting transcript: Boston, undated; [3 packets] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1965 class meeting transcript: Washington DC, undated; [4 packets] (Box 1)
  - Notice - "Art from the Vassar Class of 1965,", undated (Box 1)
  - Photograph - Sandra Walls Bond (VC 1965) and family, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1966, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate service pamphlet, 1966 Jun 4; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - "News From Vassar" notice about incoming class statistics, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1967, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "Who's Who?" photographs of 1967 in adulthood, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1968, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Baccalaureate service pamphlet, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Notice to class from Anne Phillips Dahlen (VC 1968), undated (Box 1)
  - "Our Place in History" - an essay on the class of 1968 by Antoinette Wills, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1969, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "Class of 1969 25th reunion International Auction Extraordinaire" book, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Commencement - conferring of degrees program, 1969 Jun 1 (Box 1)
  - "Professor Recollections" 25th reunion class of 1969, 1994 Jun (Box 1)
  - "Vassar Daily Vibragram" vol. 40, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1970, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - "Beards, Peace Symbols and Daisies at Vassar's Commencement" - article, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1970 commencement program, 1970 May 31 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1970 graduation photographs (Box 1)
  - Commencement - conferring of degrees program, 1970 (Box 1)
  - VC ashtray, undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1971, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1971 photographs of class, undated; [2 books] (Box 1)
  - Commencement - conferring of degrees program, 1971 (Box 1)
- Class of 1972, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Article - "Class of 1972 Idealism and Involvement," The New York Times, undated (Box 1)
  - Article - "Vassar Graduates Hear Speaker Denounce Pres. Nixon and War,", undated (Box 1)
  - Booklet - "See Here 1972" (photographs of class members), undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1972 blank mini notebook, undated (Box 1)
  - Commencement - conferring of degrees program, 1972 (Box 1)
  - "Remarks at the 1972 commencement by Elizabeth Runkle Purcell (VC 1931)," (Box 1)
- Class of 1973, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Booklet - "See Here 1973" (photographs of class members), undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1973 commencement program (Box 1)
  - Commencement - conferring of degrees program 1973 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper article on 1973 daisy chain (Box 1)
- Class of 1974, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Article - "Paddling Back to a Culture Reversed in Time,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1974 commencement program (Box 1)
- Class of 1975, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Pamphlet - "The Class of 1975 and the AAVC,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1976, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1976 commencement program (Box 1)
  - Commencement - conferring of degrees program 1976 (Box 1)
  - Pamphlet - "The Class of 1976 and the AAVC,", undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1977, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Booklet - "See Here 1977" (photographs of class members), undated (Box 1)
  - "Class of 1977 Bulletin - There and Then, Here and Now,", 1983 Jun (Box 1)
  - Class of 1977 commencement program (Box 1)
  - Class of 1977 directory for 20th reunion, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Magazine - "1977 Gives Back - 25th reunion gift,", 2002; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Obituary - Evelyn Jean Crispell (VC 1977), undated (Box 1)
- Class of 1978, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Booklet - "See Here 1978" (photographs of class members), undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1978 commencement program (Box 1)
  - Commencement - conferring of degrees program 1978 (Box 1)
- Class of 1979, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Booklet - "See Here 1979" (photographs of class members), undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1979 commencement program (Box 1)
  - "Keep in Touch" Class of 1979 directory, undated (Box 1)
  - Program - "Anyone Can Whistle,", undated (Box 1)
- Classes of 1980-2007, [0.3 cubic feet (1 box)]
  - Class of 1980 - Welcome back notice for seniors - "Schedule of First-Week Activities,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1981 - "Class of 1981 Newsletter,", 1980 Nov; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1988 - Address Register, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1988 - Article - "Alumna wants Vassar to bare her accomplishment,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1988 - Program - "Fiddler on the Roof,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1988 - senior class notes by Secretary Denise Ackerman, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1989 - AAVC invitation to class to "'89's first alumni party,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1990 - "Sporting the Oak" card, undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1991 - 10th reunion mailing list, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1993 - Library bookmark, undated; [2 copies] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1993 - "Senior Class Pictoral,", undated (Box 1)
  - Class of 1996 - "Vassar Reunion 2016" brochure (Box 1)
  - Class of 2007 - Senior class gift info - envelope, undated (Box 1)
- Printing Plates, [2.3 cubic foot (3 boxes)]
  - Class of 1868, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1869, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1870, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1871, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1872, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1873, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1874, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1875, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1876, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1877, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1878, class bookplate (Tillinghast Fund) (Box 1)
  - Class of 1878, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1879, class bookplate (Box 1)
  - Class of 1879, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1880, class tree plates and other plate (Box 1)
  - Class of 1881, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1882, class tree plates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1883, class bookplates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1884, class bookplates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1885, class bookplates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1886, class bookplates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1887, class bookplates, [2 envelopes] (Box 1)
  - Class of 1888, class bookplates (Box 1)
  - Class of 1890, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1891, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1892, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1894, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1895, class bookplates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1897, class bookplates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1899, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1900, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1901, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1902, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1903, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1904, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1905, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1906, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1907, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1908, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1909, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1910, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1911, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1913, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1913, block print used on place cards for 50th reunion dinner, 1963 Jun 7 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1914, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1915, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1916, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1917, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1918, printing plates (Box 2)
  - Class of 1919, printing plates (Box 3)
  - Class of 1920, printing plates (Box 3)
  - Class of 1921, printing plates (Box 3)
  - Class of 1922, printing plates (Box 3)
  - Class of 1923, printing plates (Box 3)